A Guide to the Records of the Office of Academic Affairs, 1961-1977 (bulk 1965-1976)
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- Series X: Records and Correspondence, 1972-1973
  - Subseries K: General Correspondence, Reports, and Papers, A-Z, 1972-1973
    - Admissions Registrar - Course Renumbering, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Admissions Registrar - Grade Distribution, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Admissions Registrar - Late Grades, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Advanced Placement Test, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - AID Programs - Venezuela, Caracas, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Association (2 folders), 1971-1973 (Box 34, Folder 16-17)
    - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - American Association of University Women, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - American Council on Education, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Annual Report, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - AUPAA - Assistant Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Athletic Association, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Automated Student Record System, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Black Students, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Board of Visitors, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Building Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Campus Buses, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Catalog Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Center for Environmental Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Centennial Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Centers for Interdisciplinary Research, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Civil Rights Issues, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Coding, 1971-1973 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Committee for Excellence in Teaching (3 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 38-40)
    - Committee on Employee Benefits, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Community Colleges, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Computer Accounts and Allotments (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 43-44)
    - Computer Center, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Computerized Student Record System, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Consortium (3 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 3-5)
    - Air Pollution, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Constitution Revision (4 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 7-10)
    - Constitution Revision Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Consulting Activities Report (2 folders), 1972 (Box 35, Folder 12-13)
    - Corps of Cadets, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Copyright Policy, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Courses taught by Departments, listings of (3 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 16-18)
    - Credit by Examination, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Credit Union, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Deans' Memos (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 21-22)
    - Department Heads (Evaluations of), 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Director of Special Academic Affairs (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 24-25)
    - Disposal of Campus Chemicals, 1971-1973 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Educational Foundation, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Employee Benefits and Insurance, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Equal Employment and Opportunity, 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Experimenting Colleges, 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Candidates, 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Handbook (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Senate (3 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 6-8)
    - Faculty Workloads, 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Federal Funds, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Final Exam Policy, 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Fort Eustis, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Founder's Day Program, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Governor's Office, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - GPAC, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Graduate Degree Program Guidelines, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - "Graduating with Distinction", 1973 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Greek Affairs Subcommittee, 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - T. Marshall Hahn (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 19-20)
    - Haiti Program (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 21-22)
    - Hard Tomatoes, Hard Times, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Honor System, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Information Services (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 26-27)
    - International Programs, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - International Student Office, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Interuniversity Communications Council, Inc (EDUCOM), 1972 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Jury Duty, 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Keller Plan, 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Labor Education, 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Laboratory Animal Care, 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Law Enforcement Education Program, 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Learning Resources Center (4 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 36, Box 37, Folder 1-3)
    - Leave (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 4-5)
    - Library (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 6-7)
    - Library Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Long-Range Goals Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Mexico Program, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Publications, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Motor Pool, 1971-1973 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - National Association of Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 13-17)
    - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators (NASPA), 1973 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - National Science Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 19-20)
    - New Faculty Orientation, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Oak Ridge Associated Universities, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - OCR Data from Colleges - Women and Minorities, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Office of Civil Rights (OCR), 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Office of Institutional Research, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 25-28)
    - Omicron Delta Kappa, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Organization Membership, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Others Colleges (3 folders), 1972 (Box 38, Folder 3-5)
    - "Outstanding Educators of America, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Outward Bound, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Patent Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Peer Grouping, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Pentagon Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Personnel Department, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Phi Delta Theta, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Philippines Program (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 13-14)
    - Philippines Program - Monthly Report, 1971-1973 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Philosophy and Religion, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Physical Plant Planting, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Physiopath, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Placement Services, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Policies, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Psychology, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Publications Distribution, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Purchasing Department, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Radiation Safety Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Rebal, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Records Administration, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Reprint Purchasing, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Requests - equipment (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 28-29)
    - Research (3 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 30-32)
    - Research Equipment Inventory, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Research Support Services, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Residence Hall Federation Congress - Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Reston (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 36-37)
    - Retirement, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Revenue Sharing, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Salaries, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Scholarships, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Self Study, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - Senate Ad Hoc Committee on the Administration, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Shaner Filer - Management Consultants (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 2-3)
    - Sloan Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools - SACS, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Southern Association of Land-Grant and State Universities, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Southern Regional Education Board (SREB), 1973 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Southwestern State Hospital, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Special Academic Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Sporn Award, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - State Board of Education, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Student Constitutional Affairs Board - Minutes, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Student Personnel Division (SPD) - General (2 folders), 1971-1973 (Box 39, Folder 13-14)
    - SPD - Counseling Center, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - SPD - Fraternities and Sororities, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - SPD - Squires, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Student Condolence Letters, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - SPD - Student Discipline, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Student Financial Aid and Scholarship, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - SPD - Student Government Association (2 folders), 1971-1973 (Box 39, Folder 21-22)
    - SPD - Student Health Services, 1971-1973 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - SPD - Student Housing (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 24-25)
    - SPD - Student Organizations, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - SPD - Student Placement Services, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - SPD - Student Programs, 1971-1973 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - SPD - Student Union, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - SPD - University Policy for Student Life, 1971-1973 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - SPD - Virginia Tech Coalition, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - SPD - "Who's Who Among Students in American Colleges and Universities", 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Student Records, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Surplus Property, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Teaching Load / A-1 Report, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Teaching Assessment: Solid Waste Management Programs - Part A (3 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 36-38)
    - Tenure, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Tenure - Faculty Summary, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Travel, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - United Nations University, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - US Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - University Awards Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - University Bookstore, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - University Center, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - University Club, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - University Controller, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - University Council, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - University Council Meeting - Minutes and Proposals, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - University Development, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - University Examination Policy, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - University Liability Policy, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - University Policies for Student Life, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Upward Bound Program (2 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 14-15)
    - Urban Mass Transportation Administration (UMTA) Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Veterans' Affairs, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Vice President Academic Affairs, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Academy of Science, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Waivers - Faculty/Staff, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Water Resources Research Center, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - W.E. Wine Award, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Weighted Student Council Hours, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Women, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Work-Study, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - YMCA, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Series XI: Records and Correspondence, 1971-1974
  - Subseries A: College of Agriculture, 1973-1974
    - Agriculture (4 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 27-30)
    - Agriculture Economics - New Faculty, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Biochemistry, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Agriculture - New Faculty, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Agriculture - Summer, 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Subseries B: College of Architecture, 1973-1974
    - Architecture, 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Architecture - New Faculty, Dickenson Appointment (3 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 36-37, Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Architecture - Report Reassessing Current and Proposed Degree Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Subseries C: College of Arts and Sciences, 1973-1974
    - College of Arts and Sciences, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - College of Arts and Sciences - Biology, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Chemistry, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Computer Science and English, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Arts and Sciences - Faculty Candidates (3 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 7-9)
    - Foreign Languages, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Geology and History, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Graduate Teaching Assistants, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Mrs. Ruth Manor - Philosophy and Religion, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Math, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Medical Technology, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Physics, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Psychology, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - ROTC - Army and Air Force, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Sociology, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Statistics, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Arts and Sciences - Summer, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Subseries D: College of Business, 1973-1974
    - College of Business (4 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 22-23, Box 42, Folder 1-2)
    - Business Faculty, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Subseries E: College of Education, 1973-1974
    - Education (9 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 4-12)
    - Administration and Educational Services - Parks, David, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Curriculum and Instruction, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Doctoral Interns, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Health, Physical Education, and Recreation, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Education Proposals, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Vocational and Technical Education, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Subseries F: College of Engineering, 1973-1974
    - Engineering (3 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 19-21)
    - Aerospace Engineering, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Chemical Engineering, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Civil Engineering, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Engineering Science and Mechanics, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Engineering Technology, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Industrial Engineering and Operations Research, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Mining Engineering, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Engineering - New Faculty, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Subseries G: College of Home Economics, 1973-1974
    - Home Economics, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Subseries H: Graduate School, 1973-1974
    - Graduate School (3 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 33, Box 43, Folder 1-2)
    - Graduate School Problems (3 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 3-5)
  - Subseries I: Extension, 1971-1974
    - Extension - Includes Task Force on Extension, 1971-1973 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Extension - CEC (5 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 7-11)
    - Extension - Off Campus Instruction, 1972-1974 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Subseries J: Research, 1972-1974
    - Research (2 folders), 1972-1974 (Box 43, Folder 13-14)
  - Subseries K: Commissions, 1973-1974
    - Commission on Faculty Affairs, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Commission on Student Affairs (4 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 16-19)
    - Commission on Undergraduate Studies (3 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 20-22)
  - Subseries L: Correspondence, Reports and Papers, A-Z, 1972-1974
    - Accounting, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Academic Guidelines Handbook, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Adjuncts, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Conference, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Admissions Records (2 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 5-6)
    - Admissions, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Affirmative Action Program (2 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 8-9)
    - AID Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Arnold Alanen - Political Science, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Distinguished Professorships, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Distinguished Professor Nominations, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Assistant Vice President for Academic Affairs (AUPAA), 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Archives Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Athletic Association, 1972-1974 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Autobatcher, 1972-1974 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Bi-racial Programs, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Board of Visitors, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Budget, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Building Committee, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Bus Service, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Calendar, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Career and Academic Advising (2 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 26-27)
    - Catalog, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Center for Energy Research, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Center for Systematic Collection, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Coding System, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Comet Kohoutek, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Commencement, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Committee for Excellence in Teaching, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Community Colleges, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Computer Allocations Summary, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Computing Center, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Conference on Articulation, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Conservation of Paper, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Consulting Activities Report (2 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 7-8)
    - Cooperative Education Program, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Copyright Policy, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Corps of Cadets, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Council of Deans, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Courses by Newspaper - Application, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Dyni, Victor P., 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Eastern Virginia Medical School (EVMS), 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Enrollment, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - EVP - Executive Vice President, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Faculty Activity Report, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Enrichment Program, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Faculty Handbook (2 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 21-22)
    - Faculty Leave Requests, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Faculty and Fellowship, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - New Faculty, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Faculty Placement Services, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Faculty Senate (2 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 27-28)
    - Federal Student Financial Aid, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - General Legal Counsel, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - General Counsel - Schotta - Dyson, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - German Student Exchange Program, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Grants: Contracts, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Grievances, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - T. Marshall Hahn, Jr., 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Haiti, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Martha Harder - Special Academic Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Honor System, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Information Sciences, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Judicial Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Laboratory Support Services Research, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Learning Resources Center (3 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 8-10)
    - Learning Resources Center - Advisory Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Library (3 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 12-14)
    - Martin, Edwin P. - Director of Special Academic Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Master of Urban Affairs, Business - Richmond, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Masterson, Father William, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Memos to the Dean (2 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 18-19)
    - Mexico (2 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 20-21)
    - Mountain Lake, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - National Career Guidance Week, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - National Institute of Education (NIE), 1974 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC), 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - The New Virginians - Stan Kingma, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - NOVA, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Nuclear Reactors, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - Ochsendwald, William L. - History Faculty Grants, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Office of Institutional Research, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Omicron Delta Kappa Honor Schedule, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Other Colleges - Available Positions, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Performing Arts and Communications (PAC) - Band, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Performing Arts and Communications (PAC) - Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Personnel, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Philippines, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Placement Services, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Policy Source Manual for Academic Administrators (Original Copy), 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Political Science, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - President Search Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Printing Services, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Proposals, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Proposals Submitted for Action Taking (2 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 15-16)
    - Research Engineer Classifications, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Reston (2 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 18-19)
    - Roanoke MBA Offering, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS), Atlanta, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Southwestern State Hospital, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Special Academic Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Susan Staples, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Student Government Association - Student Advisory Boards, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Study Abroad, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Teaching/Learning Grant Program, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Telecommunications (4 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 28-31)
    - Telecommunications Planning Sub- Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Tenure, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Tidewater Consortium, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Travel (2 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 4-5)
    - United Nations Indian Fellow Program, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - University Awards Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - University Council, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - University Development, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - University Policies for Student Life, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 10)